<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lenscas' blog</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>Recent content on Lenscas' blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 13:49:25 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Card hell post mortem</title><link>http://example.org/posts/bullet_hell_post_mortem/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 13:49:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/bullet_hell_post_mortem/</guid><description>This jam was the first time I took F# and Godot to a game jam. I never used either of them before in a gamejam, with earlier projects either using quicksilver and one simple text adventure game with just TS. I also didn&amp;rsquo;t have much experience so far with Godot, because although my main project uses it the Godot side is rather simple. Similarly, F# is a language I only use when doing Godot stuff, as this is the only context where I like it more than Rust.</description></item><item><title>F# and Godot part 2</title><link>http://example.org/posts/fsharp_and_godot_part2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 16:53:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/fsharp_and_godot_part2/</guid><description>part 1 I went over on why I chose F# and how to set it up with godot.
part 2 I will go over how you do some basic godot things in F# like emitting custom signals.
Part 3 will go deeper in F# and use it to make a library from Godot easier to use.
Setting a value through this._Ready F# is a functional style programming language at its core.</description></item><item><title>Comments</title><link>http://example.org/posts/comments/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 03:05:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/comments/</guid><description>Just a short post to tell that my blog has a comment section! 🎉 Shout out to both utteranc and github for allowing me to add comments without cost.
It is a GREAT hack that the guys over at utteranc made, and I love it.
Anyway, that is all have a great day :)</description></item><item><title>F# and Godot part 1</title><link>http://example.org/posts/fsharp_godot_part1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 01:23:40 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/fsharp_godot_part1/</guid><description>In this part I will touch on why I chose F# instead of the many other languages that I know and could&amp;rsquo;ve used with godot. In addition it also goes over on how to set it up.
Part 2 will go over how to do some basic things in Godot with F#, like how to emit signals.
In part 3 we take a bit deeper dive into F# and use some of its features to extend one of Godot&amp;rsquo;s libraries so it becomes easier to use.</description></item><item><title>Hello_World!</title><link>http://example.org/posts/hello_world/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 00:10:40 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/hello_world/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m Lenscas, just a random developer wanting to have a place to put his thoughts on. As well as put updates for projects and maybe some other stuff.
We will see :)
Expect to see content about my (still heavily in development) card game and other stuff I end up working on.
Currently planned (not in this order) :
my thoughts on Quicksilver, the libraries I made for it and its sad demise a dive into using F# with Godot.</description></item></channel></rss>